A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Office of the Vice President, Program Files FA569
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, International Division, Office of the Vice President, Program Files
1965-1970
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA569
1.4 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material is open for scholarly research, with prior archival review.
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Ford Foundation
- Robert H. Edwards Chronological Correspondence, 1965-1968; I
  - Chronological Correspondence, Sep 15-Dec 31, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Jan-Apr 1966 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, May-Aug 1966 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Sep-Dec 1966 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1967 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Apr 1967 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, May 1967 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Jun 1967 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Jul 1967 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Aug 1967 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Sep 1967 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1967 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Nov 1967 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Dec 1967 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Jan 1968 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Feb 1968 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Mar 1968 (Box 1)
- James R. Himes Subject Files, 1968-1970; II
  - Resource Base Committee, 1968 (Box 1)
  - House Committee (Burke), 1968 (Box 1)
  - Pending File, May 21, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Notes on Research in Education, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Tax Law Jazz, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Evaluation of Overseas Development Assistance, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Overseas Schools, 1969 (Box 1)
  - PRI, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Budget Folder, 1969 (Box 1)
  - UK Resource Bases for Development Trip, Nov 27-Dec 16, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Tax Information, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Black Studies, 1969 (Box 1)